(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-08T09:18:53.411529",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I was bored to tears
Felt like nine thousand years
Every back and forth and convo cut me like a knife
But then I saw it in your eyes
And it took me by surprise
Ten thousand volts, a bolt, it brought my heart to life
And I want you here right now, you know
'Cause I'm ready to let go
Get me through the night somehow
Show me all you know
My lips are a mystery
One kiss and you'll agree
If you're down to get familiarized, then
Baby, say it right
N-E-R-I-S-S-A, 'kay?
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
We're burnin' up the floor
You got a vibe I can't ignore
In a sea of embers dancin' way into the night
The best is yet to come
But you're not like anyone
How can I pass up on someone shining so bright?
But there's a scent that's filling up the air
And you're still unaware
That you're fallin' fast under my spell, baby, it isn't fair
'Cause when I'm inside this illusion
I am anyone and everyone
All logic fades away tonight
You gotta say it right
N-E-R-I-S-S-A, 'kay?
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Take me higher, it's a game
Play with fire, say my name
Say my name
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Play with fire, take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Say my name
If you want to
play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Play with fire,
Take me higher
If you want to
play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Play with fire,
Take me higher
If you want to
play the game
Yeah, you gotta
say my name
Play with fire,
Take me higher
If you want to
play the game
Yeah, you gotta say my name
Hiya darlings!
This is Hololive English Advent's devilish diva,
and today I'm here hosting a cooking show in my very own kitchen, Delicious Demonic Dishes.
As you can see, it's basically my kitchen, however,
I must tell you this is actually a replica.
If you'd like to look on the other side,
yes, you can see the Jailbirds hard at work making sure that this show goes on without a hitch.
But today is also about me, as you can see,
it's my 3D debut!
How do I look?
How is it?
Am I beautiful?
Am I kawaii?
Am I majestic?
You could look me up and down, I suppose,
starting with my lovely shoes,
going all the way up to my skirt.
And you might realize something's missing.
Since we're cooking today, I've decided to remove my jacket, so say goodbye to my wings!
But without further ado, I suppose we ought to get cooking, right? Get right on to things.
So, first, I suppose I have two lovely guests I'd like you to meet, if they'd like to come on out!
待ったかね、待ったかね、ホライブJ-Pホロッグス、あ、鷹嶺ルイだよ～
Been keeping you waiting? Hololive JP's hologs, ah, it's Takane Lui!
And then...
Hiya, ki-ki-ki! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth,
and you know something? We are birds!
Hello, tori and hello tori intern, intern!
So will you like prove yourself to us today? Mhm, oh.
So they're going to be cooking and I'm going to be cooking,
but shall we start with the first dish?
Yes, I am hungry! I'm hungry too, do you like?
Yes, I am hungry! I'm hungry too, don't you?
It's going to be making us something called Nikujaga.
Okay, Nikujaga, Japanese traditional food.
It's my first time, so I'm very excited.
Shall we get started? Let's go!
Alright, let's start make Nikujaga!
All right, let's start making Nikujaga!
I'm hungry, hungry, hungry!
Please make Nikujaga. I will make Nikujaga for Nerissa!
Yay! Oh wait, senpai, you too, don't worry, senpai too! Yes, senpai too!
So all right, here, what we will need Nikujaga is here, ingredients.
Nikujaga (Meat and Potato Stew)
Take a look, wow, memorize it down, this is Lui's personal recipe.
Alright, let's start with cutting.
All right, let's start with cutting.
Vegetable cutting.
Jaga mo kirimasu.
Cut the potatoes too.
Put them in, in the pot! Poi! Yes.
Put them in, in the pot! Toss! Yes.
Oh, so good! And fry? Right, yester...
Oh, so good! And fry? Right, yesterday...
Oh, it's already in there! Ooh!
Oh, so good! You made them appear out of nowhere!
And first, first, fry, uh, meat, meat first, first, yeah, meat first.
And then add veg- change, change the color, change the color, and cook vegetables, okay?
And then add veg— change, change the color, change the color, and cook vegetables, okay?
So not like we did it where we threw the potato in first, yeah.
Cook the meat then add the vegetables and cook them down.
Ah, it looks so good! And smell is good.
Ah, it looks so good! And it smells good.
And change the color. Oh, it's okay. Uh-huh. Good! Already? So, yeah, put water and...
seasoning.
Oh, yeah.
Ah, assistant, Elizabeth, please help.
Throw the wood.
Okay.
Hey.
Thank you!
What did you throw in there?
Yes, wooden lid.
Yes, a wooden lid.
There we go. Mm-hmm. Good.
I just stir everything.
Oh, everything, okay?
So please wait 10 minutes.
10 minutes?! 10 minutes, yes.
We'll cover... cover and get a lid for it.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
I question.
I have a question.
Why... why is it like a lid like inside and not like on the top?
Why... why is the lid like inside and not on top?
Ah, I see. Uh... um...
Ah, I see. Um...
日本語でいいですか？
Can I speak Japanese?
え、味がしみやすくね、なります。
Um, it helps the flavors soak in better.
It'll be like easier to soak in the flavor.
It'll be easier to soak in the flavor.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
All is same. More delicious.
It's the same, but more delicious.
Waku waku.
Yay.
Ten minutes wait.
10 minutes wait.
Wait? I'm waiting patiently.
It takes too long. I can't wait 10 minutes.
Yeah, I don't want to wait 10 minutes either. Can we hurry up?
Yeah, I don't want to wait 10 minutes either. Can we speed it up?
Yeah, can we use some magic maybe? To speed up the process?
That's a magic?
All right. So, please put... love.
It's magic. Chikki-chikki-chikki-chikki-bee!
After 10 minutes. Okay?
Yay!
Easy. We'll check.
Check?
Yeah, take off. Oh, it looks good.
Take soft or hard?
Is it soft or hard?
Oh, a little bit hard. Still.
So, if hard, please wait more 10 minutes.
So, if it's hard, please wait another 10 minutes.
Okay. All right. But... magic.
With a snip of a finger. Oh, yes. Okay. So...
Soft? Yes. Yes, soft. Good.
So, complete! Complete. It's finished!
胸に肉じゃが、ルイズに肉じゃが！
Nikujaga in our hearts, nikujaga for Ruisu!
It smells great, nioiyi, and it looks good, too.
It smells great, and it looks good, too.
As you guys can see, this is the real... the real nikujaga. It's real.
I'm hungry.
Me too. Ruisu... Ruisu-ne is probably hungry.
Me too. Ruisu... Ruisu is probably hungry.
Shall we try? Yeah, meshiagare!
Itadakimasu! Itadakimasu!
First ankle for carrot. Oh, um... um... um... ooh...
First, a mouthful of carrot. Oh, mm... mm... ooh...
Oishii! Oishii desu.
And like... can I use it? Yes, very good.
We have no rice now, but... yeah, today is no rice.
We have no rice now, but today there's no rice.
Without rice is also okay.
Oishii. It's like impression.
Oishii. It leaves an impression.
It makes me think it's a very homy flavor. Like... um, it feels like this is something I would eat as a kid and want to eat. Like want to come home and eat, you know, after like a long day.
It makes me think it's a very homey flavor. Like... it feels like this is something I would eat as a kid and want to eat. Like want to come home and eat, you know, after a long day.
Very good. Daizou... Daizou?
Oishii, yarakai.
Please listen. Yeah. Hmm.
Moi! Moi! Umai! Umai! Umai! Ruisu, Ruisu-san... Ruisu-senpai janakute.
Moi! Moi! Umai! Umai! Umai! Ruisu, Ruisusan... Not Ruisu-senpai.
Can you make every day for me?
Can you make it every day for me?
Every day? Yum! But easy to cooking. Yeah, she taught you. So now you can make it yourself.
Every day? Yum! But easy to cook. Yeah, she taught you. So now you can make it yourself.
Okay. Yes. But... it's so good.
I'm like really hungry. I feel like you weren't. I want to eat all. I will cook. Are you?
Okay. Oishii. Nikujaga every day. But I want to eat like fried... fried...
chicken or fillet? Right? I want to eat.
We do happen to have the queen of fried chicken with us today.
Mhm, you have to make your signature dish for us. Please! Please!
Let's go, shall we? Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
It is time to bring KFP to your kitchen. I'm going to make the best fried chicken I've ever made in my whole life.
Yes, I want to try. Why aren't you eating fried chicken?
We're missing... Thank you for the beautiful intro.
We're missing some livestock. What are we going to use?
Oh, well, I actually have the perfect thing right here.
Oh, damn it! Oh! Not Jimmy! Take me instead! Take me instead!
No, sorry, Jimmy. If anyone's qualified to do this, it's me, as a past KFP...
employee? Not anymore? Well, I mean this used to be my form, right?
I guess so. So, but now it looks like this. So, anyways, Jimmy, goodbye!
No! Jimmy, no! No! Ah, come back, Kiky! Don't save him!
Aww, it's so kawaii so-
Aww, it's so kawaii so—
Maybe I can even look. Do you think it's too big?
I think maybe it needs to be a bit smaller, don't you?
Stop the violence! Extreme violence!
Gomen, Becky desu.
Thank you, Jimmy, for your contribution.
Gosh, this is so sad.
It's okay, he'll be happy.
Is this gonna be enough for all of us?
There will, yeah. Delicious.
All right then, here we have the batter and the flour.
So I'll do this for you, okay? I'll do my best. Gambatte!
Oishiku tsukuru, I will do my best.
Let me take it up so you can see clearly.
Secret spicy? Yeah, it's got secret spices in it.
Jimmy looking shiny. Yeah, wow.
Okay, and then we go into the flour, the flour. Mmm, it's nice and golden!
As you can see, some spices were mixed onto that too, but they're secret! Secret, nice!
Okay, and with that, it's time. We have a 160 degrees Celsius heated up
oil thingy. What's it called? Deep fryer! I knew that. That was also test questions, so...
Here we go! Oh, chicken in! And my week-
No, no, no, no! That's dangerous! Oh, it's already finished? Oh, that was fast!
Here, one one? Dōzo, dōzo. Oh! Oh, that's hot! Dōzo, dōzo. Oh, it's hot!
Hot! Don't drop it! Don't drop the food!
Yay! You've got crazy hands to be able to handle that sort of Phoenix!
I guess so. It doesn't feel like anything at all. Yeah, nothing at all. Phoenix!
Thank you, Jimmy!
And now finally, the food of dreams for any KFP fan, the proper- the biggest fear.
And now finally, the food of dreams for any KFP fan, the proper— the biggest fear.
Kiara Fried Phoenix, your final form! Final form KFP, you're looking at it.
But without further ado, I really want to taste it, don't you?
Yeah. Okay, wait! Kampai! Kampai! Chicken drumsticks! Kampai!
We're really eating chicken right about now. Mmm! Mmm!
I did a good job! You do! There's like a lemony taste in it, I think. Where did the lemon come from?
Did I put lemon in there? Mushroom? Maybe we put zest?
There wasn't a batter already, probably. Oishii! Good! Yeah. No, you're the CEO.
Spice is good. I like my- my Jimmys worked for me.
Mmm. No, it's really really good. Mmm. Maybe a little bit dry.
Mine is nice and juicy. After one bite, yeah, I want more bite, yeah. More bright, more bright. I want you to eat, yeah. I want some sauce. I want sweet sour sauce. Mmm, so delicious.
I understand. Oh, yeah. It's good party food! We're having a party!
Yeah. Should we do a sleepover, too? I would like that. Yeah, you'll buy good food. Good job.
Thank you! Thank you! Arigatou shēn! Arigatou shēn! Thank you, Jimmy. Your sacrifice is letting us eat the best food ever. KFP, you're the best! Thank you for your dedication.
Thank you, Jimmy. Thank you, World. Thank you, KFP. But you know,
you guys have both cooked, but I haven't cooked anything yet, actually. So I think I have something special.
It's not technically my dish, however, it's using things from Hololive English.
So to make something Oishii desu, so if you'd like, without further ado, I would like to cook for you, so let's go! Thank you, let's go cooking! It better be good cooking for us!
Here we are, ready to make the last dish of the day, dessert. Ah, well, behind us,
we have all of the ingredients, if you'll take a look.
What I call this dish, Hololive Soup. Holo-EN Soup. It'll be good.
Huh? What? Nice, huh? Why Nerissa? Huh? No, no, no!
See, these were donated by my senpai to me, to make a soup with. I asked them, I said, "Ah, I want to make a delicious soup, so what will you give me?" And these-
See, these were donated by my senpai to me, to make a soup with. I asked them, I said, "Ah, I want to make a delicious soup, so what will you give me?" And these—
Ah, sorry, I eat one of them. Okay, see, see, see?
Let's give them a chance! Maybe- yeah. We'll try. It could be good. We don't know yet. It'll all go alright.
Let's give them a chance! Maybe— yeah. We'll try. It could be good. We don't know yet. It'll all go alright.
Yes, I guess I'll get started.
I guess I'll get started.
Oh, okay. Right into it.
Uh, we're going to be making it in this big cauldron.
We're going to be making it in this big cauldron.
Oh, magical.
And we're starting out with some chicken salt donated by Baise and Pi.
She gave it to me before as a present!
Oh my god, so sorry!
You can't do that!
Oh my god, three two one.
Take it out.
You know, I think it's fine that way.
Oh. What's next?
Ah, this is donated by Shiowee. It's an eggplant,
and it looks like Yorick, her little mascot guy.
It's so cute!
He's so cute, isn't he? So just put it...
He's so cute, isn't he? So just put it—
Right in the end.
Not cut?
Yeah, no chop, you know.
If we cook it long enough, it'll disintegrate, right?
All right, all right.
So yeah, it doesn't really make sense to cut it up,
cause it's gonna cut itself.
Like what do you have that kitchen for, right? In a knife?
We don't need that. No cutting.
And this one, can you predict who it could be from?
Ah, it says...
Uh, it says...
It's Bijou's... feet salt?
Feet flake!
Salt?
Salt flake!
Yeah! No!
So...
It's stink...
Just- just a little... Oh my god!
Oh my god! I can smell salt.
It's- it's okay. Now, we have...
It's okay? Yeah, it's okay, it's okay.
This is from Mumei Senpai.
Don't drop the whole thing.
Try to be more careful this time.
Okay. Okay.
Careful. Careful. Careful. Oh my god!
It's okay!
Daijobu! Daijobu! Daijobu! Daijobu!
Why Daijobu? Why Daijobu? Hoi de ita? No, daijobu.
We still have a sapling, which I'm sure this will absorb all the salt, right?
Got veggies. Yes.
So, first, I want to cut off this...
Oh no!
It's sad.
Sorry about your haircut.
Yeah, well, I guess that's fine. Could've cut it a bit more.
And then we just have a little bit of garnish to put on top.
How about we do it separately?
No, no, no. They're being donuts, donated by Fuwawa and Mococo, respectively.
They each gave us one, so let's go ahead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
However, it doesn't stop there. Now, we have to stir the soup.
So, we have to give it a really good stir with all those ingredients.
Look, it's coming together.
You see the color? It's like green.
Yeah, it's- it's fine. It's fine.
Look, it's not even there yet.
No, that looks like melon soda or something.
Just a little more... Oh my god!
Much better!
Fuwafwa!
Not Powfx! Murasaki soup!
Yeah.
Murasaki soup?
Hai.
Oh my god.
It's perfect. It- It looks like something from Hololive, right?
And- No. Don't- Don't you think? I'm sure it's delicious.
I- I- I don't want to eat.
Yeah? You don't want to eat it.
Niko-chan.
Is there more niko-chan? More niko-chan?
Can we just finish? So let's try it!
Oh my god! Oh my god! No, no, no. We don't want to.
Let's eat it! Let's eat it!
Let's eat it! Let's eat it! Oh my god!
It's fine. You guys have to taste it!
No!
Oh my god!
Daijobu! You don't want it?
Get back here! Oh my god!
This is- I'm- You're my Oshi so you have to.
3D debut anniversary, okay?
Okay. Okay. Okay. 3D debut.
Okay. All right.
Let's go! Let's go!
And we're finally ready. Here is the final dish, as we've served it up.
Uh, don't you think it looks delicious?
I don't even want to look.
Why? It looks good! Come on!
It's purple. It's got donuts in it. It's going to be delicious.
Looks like grape juice. That- It shouldn't look like that.
No, it's okay. Let's try it.
But, without further ado... How does it smell? How's the...?
Good point. Smell is... Okay.
The smell is okay. Smell is okay. See?
Smell is okay.
Don't knock it before you try it.
It's like burning my nostrils.
It'll be okay.
Itadakimasu.
Same timing.
What did you do to us?
I didn't do anything!
She wants to poison us!
Oh my god!
Maybe you want to take control of Hololive?
No! No!
It's not! It's really not that bad.
What have you eat- Call an ambulance!
It's not that bad, it's fine.
You delicious.
Yeah, yeah. I'll try again. See?
Maybe hers taste different.
Oh my god.
Is- Is it the same?
Yeah, same. Same. Same.
Cannot.
Sorry, there's a...
It's hearty and it's filling.
Enough! Enough!
Enough. Thank you.
Thank you.
This is not how you- you can treat your senpais.
No. No.
Congratulations, 3D debut! Congratulations!
See you!
Why are you going?
Bye-bye! Thank you. Bye-bye!
お疲れ様でした！
Good work!
Unbelievable.
I can't believe this.
Well, of course, jailbirds,
I'm sure you don't think such a thing about my cooking, right?
Surely you see it and you thought, "Ah, the brilliant purple color is wonderful!"
So, uh, won't you tell me? Won't you praise me? Come on, jailbirds, don't you like it?
Wasn't it delicious?
I guess this is my cooking show.
This is probably the pilot episode and the only episode.
So, I guess if you enjoyed, we won't be back.
So, time to distract you with a song performance!
あんたにゃ もったいない
I'm too good for you
あたしゃ本当 NICE BODY 自分に言う位
I've really got a nice body, if I say so myself
タダじゃない! じゃない?
I'm not a bad catch, am I?
熱けりゃ 冷ませばいい
If you're hot, you should cool off
淋しけりゃ EVERY BODY 誰にも わからない
If you're lonely, everybody, nobody knows
恋って いつ火がつくのか
When the flame of love will be lit
DYNAMITE 恋はDYNAMITE
Dynamite, love is dynamite
どんなに不景気だって 恋はインフレーション
No matter how bad the recession is, love is inflation
こんなに優しくされちゃ みだら
It's indecent to be treated this well
明るい未来に 就職希望だわ
My future is bright, I hope to find a job
日本の未来は
Japan's future
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
恋をしようじゃないか!
Let's fall in love!
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
なんだか もの足りない
I feel like something's missing
どこにいたって 愛してて欲しいわ
No matter where I am, I want you to love me
自分に 伝えるの 恥ずかしいじゃない!
I can tell you that myself, I'm not embarrassed!
理想の 二人だわ
We're the perfect couple
憧れよ EVERY BODY 誰しも 気づいてない
Everybody wishes they were us, nobody notices
恋愛って 夢の落とし穴
That love is the pitfall of a dream
MYSTERY 恋はMYSTERY
Mystery, love is a mystery
そんなの不自然だって 恋のインサイダー
Love's insiders say it's not natural
それでも上手になれちゃ あれわ
But if something's handled well, it'll show
幸せ来る日も キャンセル待ちなので?
Is there a waiting list for a day when happiness comes too?
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
夢があるんじゃないか!
We have dreams, right?
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
なんだか もの足りない
I feel like something's missing
どこにたって 愛してて欲しいわ
No matter where I am, I want you to love me
自分に 伝えるの 恥ずかしいじゃない!
I can tell you that myself, I'm not embarrassed!
恥ずかしいじゃない!
I'm not embarrassed!
理想の 二人だわ
We're the perfect couple
憧れよ EVERY BODY 誰んぼ 気づいてない
Everybody wishes they were us, nobody notices
恋愛って 夢の年し穴
That love is the pitfall of a dream
そんなの不自然だって 恋のインサイダー
Love's insiders say it's not natural
それでも上手になれちゃ あらわ
But if something's handled well, it'll show
幸せ来る日も キャンセル待ちなので?
Is there a waiting list for a day when happiness comes too?
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
夢があるんじゃないか!
We have dreams, right?
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
日本の未来は
Japan's future
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
恋をしようじゃないか!
Let's fall in love!
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
夢があるんじゃないか!
We have dreams, right?
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
日本の未来は
Japan's future
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
恋をしようじゃないか!
Let's fall in love!
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
Love Love Love マシーン
Love Love Love Machine
Love Love Love ステーション
Love Love Love Station
あんたにゃ もったいない
I'm too good for you
あたしゃ本当 NICE BODY
I've really got a nice body
自分で言う位 タダじゃない! じゃない?
If I say so myself, I'm not a bad catch! Am I?
熱けりゃ 冷ませばいい
If you're hot, you should cool off
淋しけりゃ EVERY BODY
If you're lonely, everybody
誰にも わからない
Nobody knows
日本の未来は
Japan's future
世界がうらやむ
The world envies
恋をしようじゃないか!
Let's fall in love!
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
モーニング娘。も
Even Morning Musume
あなたもあたしも
Even you and me
みんなも社長さんも
Everyone, even the boss
Dance! Dancin' all of the night
Oh, hiya, darlings.
I didn't quite see you there.
It's—It's not that kind of thing, though.
It's not that kind of thing, though.
Uh, welcome to my studio.
Welcome to my studio.
This is where I do all of my recording.
Of course, you've heard of it, but this is your first time being here.
But more importantly, uh, my—my little guy here...
Here? Co—Co—Coring? Coring?
Here? Coring? Coring?
Hi. Look, it's Shadow.
My baby.
My baby bird.
Isn't he cute? I know you guys are always begging to see him, so there you go.
And now that we're done cooking, I've gone ahead and put my—my jacket back on.
And now that we're done cooking, I've gone ahead and put my jacket back on.
Very nice, right? It really adds to the appeal.
But today is not only all about me. I have some wonderful special guests, if you'd like to come on out and introduce yourselves!
Hi, Daddy!
Hi!
What's up, darlings? It's your boy.
No, I'm just trying to, you know, get with the—mesh the vibe that you have going here, Nerissa.
No, I'm just trying to get with the—mesh the vibe that you have going here, Nerissa.
This place is awesome.
Yeah, you like it? Yeah.
Marine des!
Marine here!
How do you be there?
I'm so happy to have these two wonderful ladies here with me today!
Thanks for inviting us.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
We did it! 3D!
Looks so good! You look lovely!
Well, I'm so excited because we have a song we're going to be performing for all of you.
I know, a—a trio between Calliope, Marine, and Nerissa, who would have thunk it? But the team is not quite ready yet.
I know, a trio between Calliope, Marine, and Nerissa, who would have thunk it? But the team is not quite ready yet.
So, first I thought we could, uh, renshu, practice a script that we are performing because, you know, we are pro—professhinaru actors.
So, first I thought we could practice a script that we are performing because, you know, we are professional actors.
Hi. This thing... This thing, that script, that script for that thing.
Yeah, do you know—do you remember what our show is called? I sure do, but can you go ahead and—and I guess recite it for the audience who doesn't know?
Yeah, do you remember what our show is called? I sure do, but can you go ahead and recite it for the audience who doesn't know?
It is going to be... Yoisha! Yosha!
Good, good question, yeah.
Chan-chan! Look, it's—it's on here. You see?
Chan-chan! Look, it's on here. You see?
Oh, check it. Can you read?
Uh, yeah, totally. Can you read?
It's, I think, A Brush with Death: A Pirate's Tale.
So please look forward to it coming out on hololive.tv.com. Totally real site, right?
Eventually, I mean, it'll be out at some point. Oh, but oh my god, oh my god, let's go, everyone!
Let's go, let's go! You're ready.
This thing. This thing. That's a good one. Yosh. Okay, okay. Start.
This is a good one. Yosh. Okay, okay. Start.
愛の女神様！お宝を持ってきました！
O Goddess of Love! I have brought you treasure!
私…………やりました！
I... I have done it!
ごほうび……ください。
Please... give me my reward.
A wonderful job finding my lost wares, Captain.
But you must realize this was not the treasure I spoke of.
え！？
What!?
全然違います！
Of course not!
It never was. It was always about what you had, not what I lost.
この宝は全て、何千年も前に私の姉妹が盗まれたもの！
All of these things were stolen from my idiot siblings thousands of years ago!
宝はここに埋めて隠していたのですが、ある日大波が全部さらってしまった……。
I planted these here for safekeeping, and they were safe, at least until the waves took this place...
島ごと全部失くしたってこと？
You lost the whole island?
ち、違います！
N—No!
宝のありかは分かっていました！ただ……。
What I'm saying is I knew where it was the whole time! I...
God. What'd she see in you? A beautiful young woman like her, with an old hag like you?
はぁ！？
What?!
I'm young, beautiful!
I'm young and beautiful!
じゃあ私は死神ででも名乗ろうかしら。
And I'm the Goddess of Death.
「自称」なら言ったもん勝ちですものね？
Look at you, you're creeping slowly towards your grave!
Ha!?
I'm a sexy captain!
Pirate captain, um...
um...
Yes, well,
moving on, I brought you here to exact
my revenge on you, captain,
for the untimely death of your lover.
I know that you were the one to take her life,
and I will not stand for it.
You will suffer by my hands!
Ha!?
You know, this quest was just a distraction.
It was meant to keep you from watching over your
...beautiful and sexy lover,
and leave room for me to take your place.
But now your lover is dead, and I am left
with a hole in my heart.
You will pay for what you've done here and now!
That's enough of that!
Death?!
What are you doing here? Don't you usually
work the graveyard shift?
Unless you're planning on bringing back my beautiful
little bird to me, you can turn right around...
Well, maybe you don't know me
as well as you pretend to.
Or the pirate captain, as well
as you think either.
I... that's... look, you can go ahead and smite
that human if you like, I'm not going to stop you.
But I really think you might regret doing that.
You would take the side of someone so cruel
that they would take the life of their own lover?!
I expected better of you!
Besides, how am I supposed to take their place
and make that cream puff my wife if this foul killed her?
Wait!
What?
You want the captain?!
No.
Where'd you even get that from?
Why would you even think that I would want
someone as old and badly dressed as you?
But... you...
No, it has always been that treasure box of wonder,
that twintail talent, that sweet girl who can do no sin...
You? No, not at all.
Yeah, but you just called that treasure box
of wonder a hag not two minutes ago, haha!
What are you even talking about? I call this wrinkly
old wreck here in front of me a hag, not my bride-to-be.
Oh man, this is rich.
You really have no idea, do you, Nerissa?
Why are you laughing?
I'm not old! I'm 17!
Let me see if I can help you here. Maybe all
the beauty is being hidden by a mustache.
The pirate captain is a fake!
She is actually his much more beautiful lover,
who you claimed to love. Here is the Marine you thought lost.
That's not possible! I would have known
or I never would have...
I have a lot to say, but my most pressing question
is, how on earth did you not know?
You know, that's fair because they look nothing alike,
but how is I supposed to know?
It's just a mustache! I'm still cute!
Of course you are, dear. She's just an imbecile.
Anyway, my dear, her stupidity can't protect you
now that you've broken our deal. Your soul is mine!
This is all your fault, drama queen! You claimed to love
Marine, but you had no idea she was hiding behind a mustache.
Me?! How am I supposed to know? She was never
supposed to be on this quest in the first place.
Wait, if she's here, then that must mean the real
pirate captain is dead, and that's your domain, Miss Reaper.
If the captain is gone, it means you have had some
responsibility in all of this. You could have stopped this.
Innocent!
Oh, so you want to blame me for all of this?
It wasn't me who killed the captain.
I only protected Marine after she begged me to help
hide her identity from you to complete your stupid quest.
Yes, but you shouldn't have agreed to hide her.
I would have known and given her my favor without this quest.
My... soul...?
You're lucky she's here to keep me from hurting you.
I'd like to see you try. Besides, this one wasn't me.
So... I... but... bananas in his tea!
But wasn't the captain deathly allergic to bananas?!
Wow!
そういうことだったのか……。
So that's how it was...
I wanted to go on an adventure.
But he said no. So, for dessert...
Such...
Wasn't expecting that.
"I wasn't expecting that."
Unfortunately, that means that you, a human, meddled in matters of life and death.
However, after that night you, uh, helped me catch that escaped soul a few weeks back, I haven't been able to stop thinking about you.
However, after that night you helped me catch that escaped soul a few weeks back, I haven't been able to stop thinking about you.
It looks like you've already won the heart of the Grim Reaper, so consider yourself lucky.
What? Night, don't you dare!
I will protect this woman from her own crimes even in death. No one else has to know that she was the one who took the life of her lover.
It can all just be an unfortunate accident. Banana peels are known to be slippery.
Calliope!!
No! She'll never be able to escape the Reaper's clutches, and I can't allow that to happen!
After all, this is your fault, Mori, for even letting her take this deal in the first place!
But... banana...
No, Marine's doing-- that's her fault! Her fault!
If you come with me, I can protect you from even death itself.
She can't get you in the realm of the immortals.
You absolute...
But... but...
"B-But..."
Quiet!
You'll be known as the goddess who protected the banana bandit!
The others won't be very happy with you.
And you think that matters to me, why?
Ba-Banana...?
They'll blame it on her, of course.
I-- No, Marine is what I'm taking! No more talk, Nerissa!
No... Marine is what I'm taking! No more talk, Nerissa!
Think fast, Nerissa!
Not guilty!!
Wait! No, it just doesn't make sense!
Oh, thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
And good news, girls! It seems like the music team is ready for us, so why don't we head over and show them our super cool song performance?
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Is this it?
Yo, cool place you got. - Thank you.
"Yo, cool place you got." "Thank you."
荒れ狂う季節の中を 二人はひとりきり
In the season of storms, two made it by one easily
明け行く夕暮れの中を 今夜も昼下がり
in the dawning sunset, at night in the early afternoon, casually
どれほど朽ち果てようとも 最後にゃ笑いたい
No matter how bad our bodies decay, we'd love to laugh at the end of time
何のために戦おうとも 動機は愛がいい
No matter what you're fighting for, I want you to be motivated by love
新しい日々は 探さずとも 常にここに
No need to look for brand-new days, they're always here with us
色々見てきたけれども この瞳は永遠にきらり
Though I've seen a lot of things in my life, my eyes will always & forever be sparkling
あれほど生きてきたけれども 全ては夢みたい
Though I've lived my life that long, everything I've been through is like a dream
あれもこれも魅elticでも 私は君がいい
Everything looks attractive, but you're the only one for me
どこにいたの 探してたよ 連れてって 連れてって
Where have you been, I've been looking for you, take me there, take me there
何もかも 捨ててくよ どこまでも どこまでも
Giving up everything and going with you to anywhere, to everywhere
荒れ狂う 季節の中も 群衆の中も 君とならば さらり さらり
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd, with you I can go, smoothly smoothly
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
Our brand-new future, awkward past, everything will be shiny
無くしてしまったものを 振り返って ほろり
Looking back on what I had to lose... makes me weep
時には途方に暮れて ただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
Sometimes I'm lost at sea, just swaying in the wind unsteadily
息せき切ってきたの
I came running out of breath
行き先は決めたの
Already decided where to go
迷わずにいきたいけど 保証はしないよ
I'd rather not get lost but who knows
何か分かったようで 何も分かってなくて
I thought I knew something, in fact I knew nothing
だけどそれが分かって 本当に良かった
But now at least I know it and I'm so glad
新しい日々は 探さずとも 常にここに 常にここにここに
No need to look for brand-new days, they're always here with us, here with us
色々見てきたけれども この瞳は永遠にきらり 永遠にきらり
Though I've seen a lot of things in my life, my eyes will always & forever be sparkling, forever be sparkling
無くしてしまったものを 振り返って ほろり
Looking back on what I had to lose... makes me weep
時には途方に暮れて ただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
Sometimes I'm lost at sea, just swaying in the wind unsteadily
行き先決めときたの 行き先は決めたの
I thought I knew where I was going, but I decided the destination
迷わずにいきたいけど どうしようもないよ
I'd rather not get lost, but I can't help it
何か分かったようで 何も分かってなくて
I thought I knew something, in fact I knew nothing
だけどそれが分かって 本当によかった
But now at least I know it and I'm so glad
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
Our brand-new future, awkward past, everything will be shiny
荒れ狂う季節の中を 二人は一人きり
In the season of storms, two made it by one
輝きだして消えた 全ては夢みたい
Shining and fading, everything is like a dream.
あれもこれも魅力的でも 私は君がいい
No matter how attractive it is, you're the only one for me.
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where have you been? I've been looking for you.
連れてって 連れてって
Take me there, take me there.
何もかも捨てていくよ
Giving up everything and going with you.
どこまでも どこまでも
To anywhere, to everywhere.
荒れ狂う季節の中も 群衆の中も 君とならばさらさら
In the season of storms and crowds, with you I go smoothly...
新しい日々も拙い過去も全てがきらり
Our brand-new future and awkward past, everything sparkles.
Thank you guys so much!
Thank you for coming!
So fun! Thank you!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
Thank you for coming too!
Yeah, no problem. I'm happy to be here.
Grats on 3D! Thank you, made it so special to have you too as guests...
Grats on 3D! Thank you, made it so special to have you both as guests.
So, this last song for today is actually going to be the titular track of my new EP, In My Feelings.
So, this last song for today is actually going to be the title track of my new EP, In My Feelings.
Song is the same name. Uh, I really worked hard on this song. I think it came out great. So, I hope you guys will enjoy listening to my first live performance of it.
I really worked hard on this song. I think it came out great, so I hope you guys enjoy my first live performance of it.
それでは聞いてください。
So please listen.
can't believe the words that came out of your mouth
never thought that what we had would go this route
can see the clock is ticking,
but i just can't stop thinking
every little memory 's tormenting me
every little memory's tormenting me.
counting all our mistakes wanna sleep, but it won't happen
waiting for the daybreak i 'm wide awake , reliving the past and
(Waiting for the daybreak) I'm wide awake, reliving the past and
still haunted by the ghost of you
everywhere i look , it 's like you 're always there despite the fact that i 'm on my own
Everywhere I look, it's like you're always there despite the fact that I'm on my own.
i 'm in my feelings
I'm in my feelings,
like rainfall on the ground they 'soke through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me
like rainfall on the ground, soaking through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me.
i 'm in my feelings
I'm in my feelings,
it 's falling all around inside this never ending downpour , is there no escape to hope for ?
it's falling all around inside this never-ending downpour, is there no escape to hope for?
i don't even wanna look you in the eyes thinking ' bout the night you left , and your lies
I don't even wanna look you in the eyes, thinking 'bout the night you left, and your lies.
that morning i 'd awoken , my heart left bruised and broken feeling i could drown in the tears i 'd cried
That morning I'd awoken, my heart left bruised and broken, feeling I could drown in the tears I'd cried.
sinking down and alone like i 'm submerged in water
(Sinking down alone) like I'm submerged in water,
chilled straight down to the bone struggling to breath , just thinking about it
(Chilled straight down to the bone) struggling to breathe, just thinking about it.
still haunted by the ghost of you
everywhere i look , it 's like you 're always there despite the fact you left me alone
Everywhere I look, it's like you're always there despite the fact you left me alone.
i 'm in my feelings like rainfall on the ground they 'soke through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me
I'm in my feelings, like rainfall on the ground, soaking through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me.
i 'm in my feelings it 's falling all around inside this never ending downpour , is there no escape to hope for ?
I'm in my feelings, it's falling all around inside this never-ending downpour, is there no escape to hope for?
don't need you to call me , don't need you to love me
Don't need you to call me, don't need you to love me.
Don't want your weak explanation,
Know that I never met your expectations.
Now I just want you out my head,
Wanna move along, carry on, hold my head high, but
I'm in my feelings... (Feelings)
Like rainfall on the ground,
They're soaking through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me,
I'm in my feelings... (Feelings)
It's falling all around, but at the ending of this downpour, is the hope I waited for?
Yeah, I'm in my feelings, feelings...
Yeah, I'm in my feelings, feelings, ooo
At the ending of this downpour, is a rainbow I had prayed for!
No use in waving clapped!
That wasn't enough, we need jailbirds, please!
Jailbirds, do you know what time it is? Ten o'clock!
Encore!
Oh, jailbirds! You guys wanted one more song?
Ah, I see. Come, come here. Come here.
Well, I suppose if it's you guys asking, then how can I resist?
But, uh, you know, I am going to perform one more song for you. I think it's going to be super hype.
But before that, I have, uh, some important things to tell you about.
But first, reminiscing already!
Today was so much fun!
I had such a good time cooking Oden and Takanashi Kiwawa Senpai.
The nikujaga was so delicious.
Like, honestly, of everything, I think that was the most delicious thing,
and I really did fulfill my title as the Demon of Soup, because I made a really weird, mind you, soup, but it was good!
And then, getting to read that really silly script, armyding in Cali, it was so much fun!
The banana, banana, oh my god, Marien is a natural comedian,
obviously, because she's in Hololive. We're all comedians.
Uh, and I've had so much fun performing for you guys, if you enjoyed that last song, "In My Feelings," I hope you did.
Uh, I I was so happy to finally get to share that with you guys, so I hope you've enjoyed everything
that I've given you so far, but without further ado,
I do have some goods for you, or a good for you. So let's go ahead and take a look.
Ah, here it is.
So this is based off of my tuning fork, which some of you may know, some of you may not know, is also actually a microphone, but as you can see, this is a paper knife or a paper cutter.
Do you have mail that has been, you know, really annoying you as you try to open it?
You're like, "Ah, I can't get it!"
Well, this will solve that.
Do you have a problem and you just like cutting paper? This will help you too, any of your paper cutting needs.
This will help you. Again, it's pretty much a replica of my weapon, so if you think that's cool, if you want it, it also comes in a cool box.
So please do consider taking it up, uh, my paper knife.
So also, as I already mentioned before,
my EP just came out.
It's already been out for a little bit now,
but if you haven't heard it, there's three new songs.
It also includes a fourth, "Say My Name."
Which of course is already a fan favorite.
But if you haven't already, it's available on streaming services, it's available on YouTube. Please...
Let's go give it a listen.
I worked so hard on it and I'm so proud of all the songs.
Uh, of course, you heard the titular track, In My Feelings.
I I, you know, that one, I poured a lot of myself into, I think it's just so fantastic.
But there's two other songs that you have yet to hear today. So, if you haven't already, please go ahead and check it out.
Again, so proud of it and I'm hoping all of them can get to a million listens on Spotify.
So, please listen to them lots and lots and lots!
But without further ado, you guys did call me on here for an encore, so I guess I'll stop shilling and I'll start singing.
So, without further ado, please listen to Sweetest Scarlet.
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Lookin' to find the words to tell you
This feeling's brand new, tryna make do
Still, I can feel my heart is trembling
You've got me lost inside the groove
Wishing you would make a move
'Cause I can't even look away
Your eyes are shining
Still, there's something that you're hiding
Won't you tell me with the warmth of your lips?
How you found me was lonely
Then you filled my heart up, wholly
Let me know, let me know, let me know
What keeps you smilin' by my side?
If above or below me
Baby, you're my one and only
Let me show, let me show, let me show you
I can love you through the night, yeah
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Baby, you're on my mind all of the time
Yeah, you plus me, I can get behind
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
And truly, you got my heart right from the start / You fill me with your love
Standing with you beneath the moonlight
Although it's midnight
You're shinin' so bright
Longing to have you through the cold night
I've already fallen victim to your charm
Stop delaying, hold me close and warm
We'll melt into each other's arms
Don't need permission, my decision's already made clear / You can feel it from the moment we kissed
How you found me was lonely
Then you filled my heart up, wholly
Let me know, let me know, let me know
What keeps you smilin' by my side?
If above or below me
Baby, you're my one and only
Let me show, let me show, let me show you
I can love you through the night, yeah
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Ooh-ooh, la-la-la
Just want you to hold me, darling
'Cause how you found me was lonely
Then you filled my heart up, wholly
Let me know, let me know, let me know
What keeps you smilin' by my side?
If above or below me
Baby, you're my one and only
Let me show, let me show, let me show you
I can love you through the night, yeah
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Baby, you're on my mind all of the time
Yeah, you plus me, I can get behind
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
And truly, you got my heart right from the start
You fill me with your love
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Jailbirds, thank you so much for coming to my 3D debut!
I hope I was able to put on a wonderful performance for you, seeing all these flowers, it seems that was the case.
So, thank you so much, I hope you enjoyed my new music.
Uh, I hope you enjoyed my performances and seriously...
Thank you, thank you so much for coming.
I love you, Jailbirds!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye, bye, bye, bye, bye-bye!
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Jailbirds!!! Thank you for coming to my 3D debut!
This is a dream come true for me,
and I'm so happy I could share this moment with all of you,
and it's thanks to you that I'm here now ♡ THANK YOU!
Nerissa Ravencroft #3DemonDebut 3D Showcase